Guide to the Riggs Family papers, 1672-2006 MS2239
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Paper documents, circa 1785 - 2006; Series 3; 3 Linear Feet
  - Correspondence, 1832-2006; 1942-1950; Series 3 Subseries 1; 6.25 Linear Feet 12 document boxes 1 slim document box
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 October 15; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 October 16; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 October 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 October 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 October 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 November 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 November 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 November 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 November 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 November 15; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 November 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 November 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 November 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 52)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 November 25; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 November 26; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 54)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 December 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 55)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 December 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 December 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 Deceber 10; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 58)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 December 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 59)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 December 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 60)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 December 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 61)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 December 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 62)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 December 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 63)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 December 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 64)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 December 31; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 65)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 January 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 66)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 January 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 67)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 January 7; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 68)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 January 9; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 69)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 January 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 70)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 February 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 February 9; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 February 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 February 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 Feburary 15; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 February 15; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 February 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 February 21; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 February 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 February 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 February 25; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 February 26; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 February 27; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 February 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 March 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 March 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 March 9; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 March 11; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 March 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 March 15; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 March 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 March 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 March 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 March 26; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 March 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 April 1; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 April 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 April 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 April 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 April 7; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 April 10; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 April 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 April 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 April 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 April 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 April 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 April 25; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 April 27; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 April 29; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 May 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 May 6; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 May 7; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 May 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 May 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 May 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 May 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 May 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 May 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 May 27; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 May 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 May 29; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 May 31; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 June 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 June 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 June 10; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 June 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 June 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 June 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 June 27; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 June 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 July 1; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 July 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 62)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 July 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 63)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 July 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 64)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 July 11; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 65)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 July 15; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 66)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 July 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 67)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 July 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 68)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 July 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 69)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 July 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 70)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 July 29; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 71)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 August 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 72)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 August 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 73)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 August 10; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 74)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 August 11; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 75)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 August 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 76)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 August 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 77)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 August 16; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 78)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 August 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 79)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 August 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 August 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 August 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 August 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 August 26; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 August 30; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 August 30; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 September 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 September 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 September 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 September 9; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 September 11; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 September 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 September 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 September 16; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 September 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 September 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 September 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 September 30; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 October 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 October 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 October 6; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 October 6; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 October 7; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 October 11; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 October 11; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 October 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 October 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 October 21; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 October 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 October 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 October 29; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 November 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 November 11; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 November 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 November 16; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 November 16; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 November 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 November 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 November 25; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 November 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 December 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 December 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 December 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 December 16; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 December 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 December 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1945 December 30; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1946 January 6; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1946 January 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1946 August 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1946 October 26; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1948 Feburary 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1948 February 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 54)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1948 February 11; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 55)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1948 February 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 56)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1948 February 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 57)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1948 February 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 58)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1948 September 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 59)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1948 October 11; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 60)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1948 November 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 61)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1948 November 11; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 62)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1948 November 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 63)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1948 December 6; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 64)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 January 7; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 65)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 January 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 66)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 January 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 67)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 February 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 February 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 February 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 March 1; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 March 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 March 9; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      Includes picture of Edwin Mincaster, Eleanor Riggs' son and John Beverley Riggs' nephew.
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 March 15; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 March 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 March 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 March 29; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 April 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 April 25; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 April 26; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 May 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 May 9; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 May 16; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 May 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 July 31; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 August 1; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 August 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 August 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 August 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 August 15; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 August 30; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 September 6; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 September 7; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 September 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 September 15; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 September 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 September 26; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 September 26; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 October 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 October 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 October 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 October 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 October 31; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 November 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 November 7; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 November 9; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 November 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 November 21; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 December 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 December 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1949 December 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 January 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 January 9; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 January 16; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 January 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 January 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 January 30; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 February 6; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 February 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 February 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 53)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 February 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 54)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 February 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 55)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 February 26; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 56)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 February 26; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 57)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 March 6; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 58)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 March 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 59)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 March 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 60)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 March 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 61)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 March 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 62)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 March 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 63)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 March 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 March 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 March 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 March 25; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 March 29; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 April 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 April 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 April 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 8)